How does it feel,Kevin?
你觉得怎么样, Kevin?
Do you like driving on the right side?
你喜欢靠右驾驶吗?
It's a little strange.
有点儿不习惯.
Here's the turn.
要转弯了.
OK.Get into the right-hand lane.
OK. 进入右车道.
When?
什么时候?
Now!We have to make a right!
Now! 我们得向右转
But I mustn't just cut in...
但我不能超车...
We missed it.
我们错过机会了.
We have to go around.
我们得兜个圈子了.
Here's the turn.
要转弯了.
OK.Get into the left-hand lane.
OK. 进入左车道.
Left? I thought it was right.
Left? 我还以为是右边.
It is right.
是右边.
Yes.Yes. I mean a right turn.
Yes.Yes. 我的意思是向右拐.
We missed it.
我们错过机会了.
We have to go around.
我们得兜个圈子了.
No left turn.
"禁止左拐".
No turns.
"禁止拐弯".
Let's try this one.
我们试试这个路口.
No Kevin.
You can't go in here.
你不能从这里进.
Do not enter.
"不准进入".
We have to go around.
我们得兜个圈子了.
Finally.
总算成功了.
Let's get out of this car.
我们下车吧.
Kevin.
What?No Parking.
What?  "禁止停车"